http://www.spa-mart.com/company/privacy-policy.cfm

Spa AccessoriesSpa tables, LED lights and more
We also carry SpaScenes cover murals, pool table covers, and many lines of spa fragrances.
Slide Under Spa Mount
View all spa covers and lifters.
Fun and Games
View all spa & hot tub accessories.
Gulf Coast Spas
Don't see your brand here? No worries! We sell filters, covers, & chemicals for ALL spas & hot tubs.
Garden & Patio
Pool Table Covers
Planters (Coming Soon)
Outdoor Furniture (Coming Soon)
Firepits (Coming Soon)
SPA-MART.com Privacy Policy
How your information is used by America's SPA-MART.
Revised May 1, 2013.
What information do we collect?
We collect
information from you when you register on our site, place an order,
subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When
ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked
to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or
credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
; To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
; To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
; To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
; To process transactions
Your
information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever,
without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering
the purchased product or service requested.
; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
; To send periodic emails
The
email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you
information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to
receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service
information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to
unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed
unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or
access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure
server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment
gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized
with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the
information confidential.
After a transaction, your private
information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.)
will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes
(Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)
that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information
We use
cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart,
understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile
aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can
offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract
with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding
our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the
information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and
improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your
computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to
turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if
you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function
properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by
contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party
products or services on our website. These third party sites have
separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no
responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these
linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site
and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because
we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in
compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We
therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside
parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online
Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to
their information at anytime by clicking 'My Account' at the top right
corner of each page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We
are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online
Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please
also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use,
disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our
website at http://www.spa-mart.com/company/terms-of-use.cfm
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to this Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If
we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on
this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on December 29, 2016
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
America's SPA-MART aka SPA-MART.com
a division of Sonshine Covers Inc.
800-823-3618
Shopping atSPA-MART.com isSAFE & SECURE!GUARANTEED!You will pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your credit card as a result of shopping at SPA-MART.com
We guarantee that we will match any advertised price for the exact same product including the costs of tax and shipping on any product that we sell.
We Accept All
Major Credit Cards & Paypal
Talk to a live rep. Call us at (800) 823-3618
Your Privacy Is Important To Us.
We take our customers' privacy very seriously here at America's SPA-MART and take steps to ensure that the information you entrust to us is safe and out of harm's way. We store absolutely no credit card information on our servers. In fact, our staff never actually sees your credit card data. Our third-party payment gateway Cybersource is owned by Visa and all traffic to and from it are encrypted with a strong 256-bit secure SSL certificate from GeoTrust. It is also important to know how we use your browsing information and the cookies that are deployed from this site. Simply put, without cookies there is no session state from page to page so there would be no way to track what is in your shopping cart, for example. Just know that absolute no personally identifiable information is stored on that cookie and its information is not shared outside of your shopping and browsing experience at SPA-MART.com.
Don't Miss A Deal! Sign up for our Insider's Newsletter for Articles, Tips & Savings!
Copyright © 2020 America's SPA-MART   |   Terms of Use   |   Copyright Information
